http://www.x-iser.com/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Have Questions?
Contact us here at Xiser Industries
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. We will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about our customers to any third party without prior consent.
Information Collection and Use
Xiser Industries does not sell, share or rent any of the information collected on our sites to any third party in manners different from what is disclosed in this privacy policy. Below is a list of the various ways in which we collect information.
Disclosure of your Information
We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party, without prior consent. We may share non-personal, aggregate information regarding customer demographics, traffic patterns, sales, and site usage with our partners, advertisers or sponsors. We will never willfully disclose personally identifiable information about our customers to any third party without prior consent.
In special cases Xiser Industries may believe it is necessary to disclose personally identifiable information in order to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating or causing injury to or interference with Xiser Industries’ rights or property, other users, or any other party that could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose or access personally identifiable information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
Your Consent
By using the xiser.com website, those sites powered by Xiser Industries, and the services available to you on our sites, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described above. If we change our privacy policy, we will immediately post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of our policies.
Copyright © 2020 Xiser.com. All Rights Reserved
|
Privacy Policy
|
Terms and Conditions
|
Consult your Physician before any Exercise Program
